grade_3_part_1 = {
    "Intro to multiplication": [
        {
            "Find the number of objects in equal groups using skip counting and repeated addition.": {
                "Definition": "Suppose there are 3 groups of 5 similar objects, then the total number of objects can be calculated by using skip counting of 3 times of 5 steps from 5. We get the sequence 3 fives is 5, 10, 15, the total is 15.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "There are 7 boxes of 3 acrons, how many acrons in total?",
                        "Answer": "Using skip counting of 7 times of 3 steps from 3, we get the sequence 3, 6, 9, 12, 15, 18, 21. The total number of acrons is 21.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Multiplication as repeated addition": {
                "Definition": "Suppose there are 4 groups of 3 similar objects, then the total number of objects is 3 + 3 + 3 + 3 = 12, its equivalent multiplication expression is 4 x 3 = 12.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Carlos writes the expression 8 + 8 + 8 to show the number of chocolate chips in 3 cookies. What is the equivalent multiplication expression?",
                        "Answer": "There are 3 eights, thus the multiplication expression is 3 x 8",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Multiplication on the number line": {
                "Definition": "For example to calculate 5 x 4, we can use number line where the starting point is 0, then we move 5 times, each time of 4 spaces. Thus, we end up at a position 4 + 4 + 4 + 4 + 4 = 20 so 5 x 4 = 20",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Compute 3 x 8?",
                        "Answer": "Use number line where the starting point is 0, we move 3 times, each of time of 8 spaces and end up at position 8 + 8 + 8 = 24.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Multiplication as groups of objects": {
                "Definition": "Suppose there are 9 groups of 4 similar objects, then the total number of objects can be calculated with 9 x 4 = 36.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "There are 4 circles of 8 ducks, how many ducks in total?",
                        "Answer": "As each circle have the same number of ducks, the total number of ducks is 4 x 8 = 32 ducks.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Commutative property of multiplication": {
                "Definition": "The commutative property of multiplication is a rule that says that we can change the order of the factors in a multiplication problem and still get the same product. For example, 3 × 4 = 12 and 4 × 3 = 12. This property helps us to remember and learn multiplication facts more easily.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Find the missing number in the equation 6 x 2 = ... x 6",
                        "Answer": "Based on the commutative property of multiplication, 6 x 2 = 2 x 6, thus we conclude that the missing number is 2.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "The garden has 8 pots, there are 2 flowers in each pot. Mark multiplied 8 × 2 to find the total number of flowers. Emma multiplied 2 × 8 to find the total number of flowers. Who is correct",
                        "Answer": "Based on the commutative property of multiplication, 8 x 2 = 2 x 8, thus we conclude that both are correct.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        }
    ],
    "1-digit multiplication": [
        {
            "Multiply by 0 or 1": {
                "Definition": "Anything multiplied by 1 stays the same, and anything multiplied by 0 is just 0.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "What is 1 x 2?",
                        "Answer": "2",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "What is 1 x 0?",
                        "Answer": "0",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Distributive property": {
                "Definition": "The distributive property is a rule in math that says we can break a multiplication problem into two or more smaller problems, and then add the results together to get the same answer. This is helpful for multiplying larger numbers because it lets us break the problem down into smaller, more manageable chunks. For example, if we want to multiply 8 × 12, we could use the distributive property to break it down like this: 8 × 12 = (8 × 10) + (8 × 2) = 80 + 16 = 96.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "How to use distributive propert to compute 9 x 7?",
                        "Answer": "9 × 7 = (10 × 7) − (1 × 7) = (10 × 7) − (1 × 7) = 70 - 7 = 63",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "How to use distributive propert to compute 9 x 4?",
                        "Answer": "9 × 4 = 10 fours - 1 four = 40 − 4 = 36",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Use skip counting to help when multiplying by doubles": {
                "Definition": "Skip counting can be really helpful when multiplying by doubles, or by any number really! When multiplying by 2, we can skip count by twos to get our answer. For example, if we want to find out what 2 × 6 is, we can count by twos six times: 2 , 4, 6, 8, 10, 12. So 2 × 6 = 12.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "How to use skip count to calculate 4 x 7?",
                        "Answer": "When multiplying by 4, we can skip count by fours. So to find out what 4 × 7 is, we can count: 4, 8, 12, 16, 20, 24, 28. So 4 × 7 = 28.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        }
    ],
    "Addition, subtraction, and estimation": [
        {
            "Rounding to nearest 10 or 100": {
                "Definition": "To round a number to the nearest 10, identify the digit in the ones place and round up if it's 5 or greater, or round down if it's less than 5. For rounding to the nearest 100, focus on the tens digit and round up if it's 5 or greater, or round down if it's less than 5.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Round 492 to the nearest hundred.",
                        "Answer": "5000",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "What is the largest whole number that will round to 80 if we're rounding to the nearest ten?",
                        "Answer": "84",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Estimate to add multi-digit numbers": {
                "Definition": "Suppose we want to add 235 and 286, we might round both numbers to the nearest hundred and estimate that the sum is around 500.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "What is the estimated result of 223 + 129 using rounding technique?",
                        "Answer": "We round both numbers to the nearest tens, which is 220 and 130, then the estimated sum is 350.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Add 3-digit numbers by breaking apart": {
                "Definition": "One strategy is to break apart each of the numbers into three parts: the hundreds, the tens and the ones.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "How to compute 374 + 152",
                        "Answer": "We can break each number into 3 parts, which is 300 + 100 + 70 + 50 + 4 + 2 = 526.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Adding using groups of 10 or 100": {
                "Definition": "One strategy is to break apart one of the numbers and make tens or hundreds.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "How to compute 247 + 794?",
                        "Answer": "To add 247 + 794, we can break apart the 247 into 6 and 241. Then, we can add 794 + 6 to make 800, and add the remaining 241 to get a final answer of 1041.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Estimate to subtract multi-digit numbers": {
                "Definition": "Suppose we want to subtract 273 from 678, we might round both numbers to the nearest hundred and estimate that the subtraction is around 400.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "What is the estimated result of 532 - 104 using rounding technique?",
                        "Answer": "We round both numbers to the nearest tens, which is 530 and 100, then the estimated sum is 430.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Subtract 3-digit numbers by breaking apart": {
                "Definition": "One strategy is to break apart each of the numbers into three parts: the hundreds, the tens and the ones.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Compute 535 - 321",
                        "Answer": "We can break each number into 3 parts, which is (5 hundreds + 3 tens + 5 ones) - (3 hundreds + 2 tens + 1 one) = 5 hundreds + 3 tens + 5 ones - 3 hundreds - 2 tens - 1 one = 2 hundreds + 1 ten + 4 ones. Thus, the result is 214.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Regrouping when adding or subtracting": {
                "Definition": "When we regroup, we carry over numbers from one place value to another. For example, when we add 38 and 47, we end up with 15 in the ones place. But we can't write 715 as the sum because we only use one digit in the ones place. So we regroup by carrying over the 10 from the 15 into the tens place, which gives us a sum of 85. This also work with subtraction.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Compute 802 - 134",
                        "Answer": "668",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        }
    ],
    "Intro to division": [
        {
            "Division as equal groups": {
                "Definition": "Division is a way of sharing or grouping things equally. In math, we often write it with the division symbol, /. For example, 6 / 2, means we are dividing 6 into 2 equal parts.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "There are 63 milk cartons. Each box holds 7 milk cartons. How many boxes of milk cartons are there?",
                        "Answer": "63 / 7 = 9",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Relating multiplication and division": {
            "Definition": "Division and multiplication are basically opposite operations. Multiplication involves taking two numbers and combining them to create a larger number. For example, 3 × 4 or 4 × 3 results in 12. Division, on the other hand, takes one number and breaks it into a certain number of equal parts. For example, 12 / 4  results in 3.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Compute 32 / 8 using the relation with multiplication?",
                        "Answer": "32 / 8 = 4 because 4 x 8 = 32.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        }
    ],
    "Understand fractions": [
        {
            "Fractions intro": {
                "Definition": "A fraction is a way of representing a part of a whole. The top number is called the numerator, and the bottom number is called the denominator. The numerator is the number of equal parts being counted. The denominator is the number of equal parts in one whole.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "If a pizza has 8 equal pieces, what fraction of the pizza is 1 piece?",
                        "Answer": "1 eighth, or 1/8",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            },
            "Fractions and whole numbers": {
                "Definition": "when the numerator is bigger than the denominator, it means that the fraction is bigger than 1. For example, 4/3 is greater than 1 because the number of pieces we are counting, 4 is greater than the number of pieces in the whole, 3.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "If a circle has 6 equal pieces and each circle represents 1 whole. What fraction does the total area of all pieces represent?",
                        "Answer": "12 sixths",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    },

                    {
                        "Question": "Each large square is 1 whole and contains 3 blocks. What fraction describes the 3 wholes?",
                        "Answer": "9/3",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Fractions on the number line": {
                "Definition": "We can divide the number line into different parts to show where a fraction falls. For example, if we divide the number line into four equal parts, we can show 1/4 halfway between 0 and 1/2.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "The line between point 0 and point 1 is seperated into 4 equal parts, thus there are 3 points between 0 and 1. What fraction is located at point 3",
                        "Answer": "3/4",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Fractions and relation with 1": {
                "Definition": "A fraction is greater than 1 when the numerator is greater than the denominator. A fraction is equal to 1 when the numerator is equal to the denominator. A fraction is less than 1 when the numerator is less than the denominator.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Compare 1 vs 1/2",
                        "Answer": "1 > 1/2",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Compare 1 vs 5/2",
                        "Answer": "1 < 5/2",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        }
    ]
}

grade_3_part_2 = {
    "Equivalent fractions and comparing fractions": [
        {
            "Equivalent fractions": {
                "Definition": "Equivalent fractions are fractions that look different but represent the same amount. For example, 1/2, 2/4, and 3/6 are all equivalent fractions.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Compare 1/6 vs 2/12",
                        "Answer": "1/6 = 2/12",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Compare fractions with the same numerator": {
                "Definition": "When comparing fractions with the same numerator, the fraction with the smaller denominator will be larger. For example, if we compare 1/2 and 1/4 we can see that 1/2 is larger because the denominator is smaller (so the single \"part\" is larger).",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Compare 1/6 vs 1/4",
                        "Answer": "1/6 < 1/4",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Compare fractions with the same denominator": {
                "Definition": "When comparing fractions with the same denominator, the fraction with the larger numerator will be larger. For example, if we compare 2/4 and 3/4 we can see that 3/4 is larger because the numerator is larger (so there are more \"parts\" in this fraction).",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Compare 1/4 vs 2/4",
                        "Answer": "1/4 < 2/4",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Comparing fractions of different wholes": {
                "Definition": "When comparing fractions of different whole, we need to change a whole to be an equivalent form with another whole, or determine which whole is larger. If we cannot do it, we conclude that it cannot be determined.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "My unicorn ate 2/6 of a pizza from Store A. I ate 1/3 of a different pizza from store B. Who ate more pizza?",
                        "Answer": "As we do not know whether the size of pizza from Store A is equal to the size of pizza from Store B or not. Thus, we cannot determine who ate more pizza.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "It took Hiro 1/3 of an hour to run from his house to school. It took Fred 1/3 of an hour to run from his house to school. Who took more time running to school?",
                        "Answer": "As both took 1/3 of an hour, they took the same time running to school.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Amir ate 2/3 of a piece of red licorice. Nikko ate 2/3 of a longer but equally thick piece of red licorice. Who ate more red licorice?",
                        "Answer": "The piece of red licorice that Nikko ate is larger than the piece of red licorice that Amir ate, thus 2/3 of the piece that Nikko ate is also larger than 2/3 of the piece that Amir ate. Thus, Nikko ate more red licorice.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        }
    ],
    "More with multiplication and division": [
        {
            "Multiplication and division word problems": {
                "Definition": "In order to solve a problem with words, we should always read the problem carefully, and make sure we understand what it's asking us to do. We can also write out equations to help us organize our work.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Sidra and her sister have 20 minutes to play with their new hula hoop before dinner. They split the time evenly. How long will they each get to play with the hula hoop?",
                        "Answer": "Sidra and her sister have 20 minutes to play and they split the time evenly, thus each of they will play with the hula hoop in 20 / 2 = 10 minutes.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "On one table at a book fair, there are 3 rows of books with 6 books in each row. What is the number of books on the table?",
                        "Answer": "The total number of books is the multiplication of number of rows times the number of books in each row, thus the total number of books on the table is 3 x 6 = 18 books.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Associative property of multiplication": {
                "Definition": "The associative property of multiplication means that when we multiply three or more numbers together, we can group them in any way we want and still get the same answer. For example, (2 × 3) × 4 is the same as 2 × (3 × 4). The associative property of multiplication tells us that we can group factors in different ways and still get the same product. For example, when multiplying with a 2-digit number, we can use the associative property to break down the 2-digit number into separate 1-digit multiplications.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Compute 45 x 64",
                        "Answer": "To compute 45 x 64, we can apply division and associative property of multiplication for easier calculation. Specifically, 45 x 64 = 5 x 9 x 4 x 4 x 4 = (5 x 4) x 4 x 4 x 9 = 20 x 4 x 4 x 9 = 80 x 4 x 9 = 320 x 9 = 2880.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Multiplying by tens": {
                "Definition": "When you multiply a number by ten, you are essentially just adding a zero to the end of the number. This is because of how place value works. For example, consider the number 34. The \"3\" is in the tens place, and the \"4\" is in the ones place. When you multiply 34 by 10, you end up with 340. The \"3\" has shifted over to the hundreds place, the \"4\" has shifted to the tens place, and the new zero is now in the ones place. This pattern holds true for any whole number: when you multiply by ten, you just add a zero to the end. This makes multiplying by ten relatively easy compared to multiplying by other numbers.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Compute 234 x 10",
                        "Answer": "2340",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Part of the castle needs repairs. 4 walls need to be rebuilt, and 50 bricks are needed for each wall. How many bricks are needed in all?",
                        "Answer": "The total needed bricks is 4 x 50 = 4 x 5 x 10 = 20 x 10 = 200 bricks.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        }
    ],
    "Arithmetic patterns and problem solving": [
        {
            "Two-step expression word problem": {
                "Definition": "A 2-step expression is a math problem that requires two steps to solve. For example, 3x + 2x is a 2-step expression. To solve it, we first add 3x and 2x, together to get 5x and then we can solve for x.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Dikembe scored 8 points during each of the first 3 quarters of his basketball game. During the last quarter Dikembe scored 11 points. Find the total number of points (p) Dikembe scored during the game?",
                        "Answer": "p = 8 x 3 + 11 = 24 + 11 = 35 points",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Hiro has 28 marbles. If Hiro divides the marbles into bags of 8 marbles, there will be 4 marbles left over. How many bags of 8 marbles can Hiro make?",
                        "Answer": "We have the equation 28 = 8x + 4 where x is the number of bags that we need to find, then solving x = (28 - 4) / 8 = 24 / 8 = 3. Thus Hiro can make 3 bags of 8 marbles",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Two-step estimation word problem": {
                "Definition": "In word problems, we can use estimation to help us check our work. For example, if we're trying to find out how many apples there are in 11 bags, each with 6 apples, we can estimate that there are about 60 apples. If we calculate the exact answer and get 15, we know we've made a mistake.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Sal's book is 52 pages. Sal already read 18 pages. He plans to read 10 pages each day until he finishes the book. Estimate how many days it will take Sal to finish reading the book.",
                        "Answer": "By estimation, 52 is approximate to 50 and 18 is approximate to 20, thus Sal has 30 pages to read. As he plans to read 10 pages each day, he will finish reading the book in 30 / 10 = 3 days",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Patterns in arithmetic": {
                "Definition": "Patterns in arithmetic are sequences of numbers that follow a certain rule. For example, the sequence 2, 4, 6, 8, 10 is a pattern in arithmetic because we're adding 2 to each number to get the next one.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "What is the sum of an even number and odd number?",
                        "Answer": "Always odd.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Find the missing number in the pattern: 30, 45, 60, _, 90, 105",
                        "Answer": "This sequence is a pattern in arithmetic by adding 15 to each number to get the next one. Thus, the missing number is 60 + 15 = 75",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        }
    ],
    "Area": [
        {
            "Count unit squares to find area": {
                "Definition": "Area is the space inside of a two-dimensional shape. We can also think of area as the amount of space a shape covers. For example, a rectangle with 2 rows, each row has 6 unit squares. The unit squares are labeled 1 through 12. This rectangle has an area of 12 square units because it covers 12 square units.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Figure A has 3 rows and 6 columns of 11 unit squares connected together. Top row has 6 unit squares, middle row has 3 unit squares, and the bottom row has 2 unit squares. Figure B has 5 rows and 4 columns of 14 unit squares connected together. The top 2 rows have 1 unit square each and the bottom 3 rows have 4 unit squares each. Which figure has the larger area?",
                        "Answer": "As each unit square is of the same size, Figure B has larger area.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Area of a rectangle formula": {
                "Definition": "To find the area of a rectangle, we multiply the length of the rectangle by the width of the rectangle. Area of rectangle = length × width.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "A square with the top side labeled 2 meters. What is the area of this square?",
                        "Answer": "A square is a rectangle, thus the area of square = 2 × 2 = 4 square meters.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Shreya and Tim are setting out to explore with their treasure maps (shown below).\nShreya: A rectangle with the left side labeled 7 meters and the top side labeled 10 meters. Tim: A rectangle with the left side labeled 8 meters and the top side labeled 9 meters. Which treasure map has the larger area?",
                        "Answer": "Shreya's map has the area of 7 x 10 = 70 square meters, Tim's map has the area of 8 x 9 = 72 square meters. Therefore, Tim's treasure map has the larger area.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "This cat and bird picture has an area of 56 square centimeters. The height of the picture is 7 centimeters. What is the width of the picture?",
                        "Answer": "The width of the picture = area of the picture / height of the picture = 56 / 7 = 8 centimeters",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Hiro and Nikko each has a LEGO block with the width of 5 centimers, but Hiro's LEGO block has the height of 8 centimers and Nikko's LEGO block has 3 centimers. They now combine their own LEGO block into 1 single block. What is the total area of the new LEGO block?",
                        "Answer": "The area of the new LEGO block = 5 x (3 + 8) = 5 x 11 = 55 squared centimeters.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        }
    ],
    "Perimeter": [
        {
            "Perimeter of polygons": {
                "Definition": "Perimeter is the distance around the outside of a two-dimensional shape. To find the perimeter of a shape, we add all of the shape's side lengths. For example: a trapezoid with sides labeled as follows: 18 meters, 8 meters, 10 meters, and 10 meters, its perimeter is 18 + 8 + 10 + 10 = 46 meters.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Lulu has exactly enough fencing to go around her rectangular garden. She has 40 meters of fencing. The garden is 8 meters wide. What is the length of her garden?",
                        "Answer": "The length of her garden is also the perimeter of the rectangular garden, which is 40 + 8 + 40 + 8 = 96 meters.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Use perimeter to find missing length of side polygons": {
                "Definition": "Sometimes we might need to use clues from the shape to figure out the missing side length. For example, if we know that a square has a perimeter of 16, we can divide by 4 to find that each side must be 4 units long.",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "A six-sided polygon with the sides labeled as follows: 14 centimeters, 10 centimeters, 4 centimeters, 8 centimeters, 8 centimeters and one side with question mark centimeters. The perimeter of the figure is 50 centimers. What is the length of the missing side?",
                        "Answer": "Let x be the length of the missing side, we have the perimeter equation: 50 = 14 + 10 + 4 + 8 + 8 + x = 44 + x, solving this we have x = 6. The length of missing side is 6 centimeters.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        }
    ],
    "Measurement": [
        {
            "Mass": {
                "Definition": "Mass is the amount of matter in an object. We usually measure it in grams (g) or kilograms (kg).",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "A walrus at the aquarium is weighed once a month. His weight for May is 850 kg. In June, the walrus weighed 63 kilograms less than he did in May.",
                        "Answer": "The mass of the walrus in May is 850 kilograms. The walrus weighed 63 kilograms less in June than he did in May. We can find the mass of the walrus in June by subtracting the weight the walrus lost (63 kg) from the mass of the walrus in May (850 kg), which is 850 - 63 = 787 kg. The walrus weighed 787 kilograms in June.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        },
        {
            "Volume": {
                "Definition": "Volume is the amount of space an object takes up. We can measure it in units like milliliters (mL) or liters (L).",
                "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Maricel drank her entire 50 milliliter sports drink during her 10 kilometer race. Every kilometer Maricel drank the same amount. How many milliliters did Maricel drink each kilometer?",
                        "Answer": "We can find the number of mL Maricel drank each kilometer by dividing the total number of mL by the number of kilometers she ran, which is 50 / 10 = 5 mL. Therefore, Maricel drank 5 mL of her sports drink every kilometer.",
                        "Type": "",
                        "Difficulty": 1
                    }
                ],
                "Rate": 1
            }
        }
    ]
}